지난 시간의 '프렌즈'...
-Previously on Friends....
-I don't feel like I have a girlfriend.
내가 애인이 있는지도
모를 지경이야
그럼 직장 그만두고 맨날
애인 노릇이나 해?
You want me to quit my job so you
can feel like you have a girlfriend?
마크 때문이야?
-ls this about Mark?
-Oh, my God.
맙소사!
아니군
-Okay, it's not.
-Oh, my God.
세상에! 난 더 이상
같은 문제로 다투기 싫어
I cannot keep having this
fight with you!
나도 몰라! 모른다구!
우리 시간 좀 갖자
Maybe we should just take a break.
좋아, 좋지, 그래
잠깐 쉬자, 진정하자구
Fine. You're right.
Let's take a break.
Let's get some frozen yogurt
or something.
시원한 콜라나 마실까?
아니, 우리 관계 말이야
A break from us.
Then we had this big fight,
and I said I wanted to take a break.
그리고 엄청나게 싸웠어
잠시 만나지 말자고 했어
그건 진심이 아니었어
I don't want to take a break.
우리가 미쳤었나봐
우리 잘 해결해보자
This is crazy.
Can't we work on this?
마실 거 줘?
What do you want to drink?
Who's that?
누구야?
아냐
Nobody.
Is that Mark?
마크지?
Honey, look, he just
자기야... 마크가...
그래, 알았어
Yeah. Got it!
함께 춰요
유부남이에요?
Hey, come dance.
What, are you married?
그럼 괜찮죠
Because that's okay.
다음날 아침
- 안녕
How was the big anniversary dinner?
어제 저녁은 어땠어?
Well, we never actually got to dinner.
저녁은 먹지도 못했어
대단했나봐?
Nice.
We kind of broke up instead.
아니, 헤어지기로 했어
What?
뭐?
세상에!
천장에 다 튀었어
My God!
It's on the ceiling!
괜찮아,
주스보다 중요한 얘기잖아
That's okay.
This is more important than fruit...
천장 좀 봐
...on my ceiling.
정말 헤어졌어?
You broke up?
Yeah, but it's okay because
when Ross left, Mark came over.
응, 근데 로스가 가고
마크가 왔어
- 뭐! 마크 때문이야?
- 아냐, 아냐, 진정해
-Oh, no! You and Mark?
-It's okay. Calm down.
마크와 얘기하다...
Mark and I talked...
바보 같은 네 오빠를
더 사랑하게 됐어
...and I realized how much
I love your stupid brother.
We got our problems,
but I really wanna make it work.
문제가 있긴 하지만
잘 해결되리라 믿어
좋은 아침!
Morning!
The One the Morning After
안녕, 나야
It's me. I've been trying
to reach you all night. I feel awful.
어젯밤 내내 전화했어
끔찍한 기분이야
나하고 마크는
아무 사이도 아니야
There's nothing between me and Mark.
어제 일은 말도 안돼
This whole breakup thing
is just stupid.
맞아!
자기를 너무
몰아 부친 거 같아
I'm sorry I put you through it.
우리 다시는
이런 전화 하지 말자
And I don't want to get
back together over a machine.
- 자기, 사랑해
- 나도 사랑해
So I love you.
I love you.
지금 잘 건데
And you know what?
I'm gonna go to bed now...
내일 아침, 출근 전에
8시 반쯤 거기 들를게
...but on my way to work tomorrow,
I'll stop by around 8:30. Bye.
잘 자
클로이? 서둘러
Chloe, how's it coming?
어떤 강아지를 키우면
좋을까요?
What kind of puppy do you think
I should get?
나도 모르지, 큰 개로 사
Well, how about a big one?
-But my apartment's so
-Then a small one.
- 우리 집은 너무...
- 그럼 작은 개를 사
- 어서 가주면 좋겠어
- 잠깐! 내 신발은요?
-We have to go.
-Wait! Where's my shoes?
꼭 신어야 돼?
You need shoes?
알았어
왜 그렇게 서둘러요?
-Do I know why we're rushing?
-You know my girlfriend?
어제 내 여자친구 얘기했지?
나와 다시 잘해보고 싶대
It turns out that she wants
to get back together.
찾았다!
I found it!
- 정말 잘 됐어요
- 응
That's so great for you guys!
You must be so happy!
기쁘겠어요
물론이지
최고로 행복해...
Yes, I am. One of the many
things I'm feeling.
-Good luck with your girlfriend.
-Thank you.
둘이 잘 되길 빌어요
고마워, 그럼...
레이첼!
안녕
- 메시지 들었지?
- 응, 아주 딱 맞춰 왔네
-You got my message?
-You are right on time!
So can I be your girlfriend again?
자기는 어때?
나, 자기 여자친구 맞지?
당연하지!
Yes, you can. Very much.
안녕
- 왔어?
- 천장은 왜 닦니?
-Why are you mopping your ceiling?
-There's banana on it.
바나나가 튀었어
나한테도 그런 능력이
있으면 좋겠다
I have the spirit of an
old lndian woman living in mine.
So, then, you know.
그럼 좋을까?
The mailman was here,
so I brought your mail.
- 올라오다가 편지를 가져왔어
- 고마워
-Oh, good. Thanks.
-Now, what is Fabutech?
패뷰텍이 뭐야?
Don't judge me too much, okay?
오해하지 말고 들어
I saw this infomercial,
and I swear I have never...
난 쇼핑채널에 전화해서
물건을 사는 여자는 아냐
... bought anything on TV before.
Except for this mop.
이 대걸레만 빼고!
그런데 다리털 제거하는
왁스가 나오더라구
But there was this amazing stuff
on leg-waxing
Waxine!
- 왁신?
- 본 적 있어?
Yes! Have you seen it?
놀랍다!
나도 너무 사고싶었어
It's incredible!
I want to be a Waxine Girl!
I know!
그렇지!
Do you think it really doesn't hurt?
How can they do that?
많이 아프지 않을까?
잘 되긴 할까?
Hello! Organic substances recently
discovered in the rain forest?
열대림에서 최근에 발견한
유기물질이랬어
They have the best stuff in there.
그럼 최고겠네
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
네가 안보이길래
레이첼한테 간줄 알았어
We figured when we couldn't find you,
you'd gone to make up with Rachel.
그래야 되는 거 아니었어?
Which is probably what
you should have done.
말이라고 하냐?
You think?
젠장, 끔찍해
이제 어떻게 하지?
God, I'm in hell.
I mean, what am I gonna do?
레이첼은, "사랑해, 우리 이제
잘 지내"라고만 하는데
Rachel's all "I love you,"
and all I can think about...
내가 한 짓을 알게되면
뭐라고 하겠어?
...is what is she gonna do
when I tell her what I did?
First, we should address
the more important question...
그 말에 답하기 전에
먼저 짚고 넘어갈 게 있어
네 멍청지수가 얼마냐?
...how dumb are you?
Look, we're trying to
rebuild a relationship here, right?
뭐? 지금, 내가 이 상황을
어쩌냐는 거야
서로 솔직하지 않고서
처음처럼 될 수가 있어?
How can I do that
without being honest?
I'm onboard about
the total-honesty thing. I am.
솔직함에 관해선
나도 동감이야
Just not about stuff that's
gonna get you in trouble.
하지만 네가 겪게 될
일을 생각해야지
He's right. Nobody benefits,
and you'll just hurt her.
그래, 솔직해봐야 레이첼의
마음만 아프게 돼
그렇게 되면
레이첼이랑은 끝이야
And there won't be a relationship
left to rebuild.
- 그렇지만...
- 우리도 알아
Don't you think
솔직히 털어놓고 싶으면
때를 기다렸다가 해
If you have to tell her,
at least wait till the timing's right.
And that's what deathbeds are for.
그건 죽기 전에 하는 거야
- 알았어
- 됐어
-Yeah, okay.
-All right.
이제 할 일은 레이첼이
다른 데서 듣지 않게 해야돼
Okay. Now, we just have to make sure
she doesn't find out some other way.
Did you think about the trail?
경로를 생각해 봤어?
What trail?
무슨 경로?
너의 여자가, 네 여자 공범을
몰라야 하잖아
From the woman
you did it with...
...to the woman you hope
never finds out you did it!
Always think about the trail!
말이 샐 경로를 생각해 봐!
별... 경로는 없을 거야
I don't think there's any trail.
그래...
클로이는 아이작과 일하지
아이작 동생이 자스민이고
Chloe works with that guy, lsaac.
Isaac's sister is Jasmine, who works
at the massage place with Phoebe.
자스민은 피비와 같은
마사지 가게에 다녀
피비는 레이첼의 친구...
그게 바로 경로야!
Phoebe is Rachel's friend,
and that's the trail! I did it!
내가 찾았다!
"After applying the Waxine
and linen strips to leg"
왁신을 바르고, 시트를
1번 다리에 붙인다
Did that!
했어!
시트 끝을 잡고, 통증을
못 느끼게 재빨리 떼어낸다
"Grasp the linen strip by its tab...
...and pull it off in one quick,
pain-free motion."
알았어
Was it not "pain-free"?
'무통증' 아냐?
No, it was pain-ful!
아니, '무한 통증'이야!
이름 바꿔야겠어
'왁스와 함께 통증을'
My God, they should call it
"Pain-zine, now with a little wax."
The girls on the commercial
don't seem to think it's that bad.
광고에 잠옷입고 나온
여자들은 엄살 안 떨던데
Because their nerves are
deadened from being so stupid.
광고에서 웃어야 하니까
신경이 죽은 척 한 거지
내가 엄살인 거 같으면
어서 해보시지
But you know, if you don't
believe me, please, be my guest.
세상에!
다리털인 게
다행이다 싶지?
Now are you glad we didn't start
with the bikini strips?
Chloe, hi.
클로이, 안녕
시계 때문에 온 거죠?
Is this about me taking your watch?
-You took my watch?
-I'm sorry. I do that.
- 내 시계 가져갔어?
- 미안해요, 내가 그래요
그냥 가져, 있지...
우리 얘기 누구한테 했니?
You keep it. Listen, did you
tell anyone about us?
I feel like it really isn't
anybody's business.
아뇨, 다른 사람이
알 필요 없잖아요
Exactly. So you didn't
mention anything to lsaac?
그래, 아이작도 모르는 거지?
-I tell lsaac everything.
-You do? Of course you do.
아이작한테는 다 말해요
그래? 그렇구나
아이작, 아이작...
안녕하세요?
Hi, lsaac.
You know, we haven't actually met.
- 우리가 그리 친하진 않지만
- 당신 개야!
You dog!
Yes, I suppose I am a dog. But see,
I happen to have a girlfriend.
네, 개만도 못하죠
난 여자친구가 있어요
커피숍에 있던 레이첼이죠?
Right. Rachel from the coffee place.
That's the one.
Listen, I don't want to hurt her.
맞아요, 그녀를 아프게
하고 싶지 않아요
당연하죠, 사랑이 문제가
아니라 일부일처가 문제죠
I know. It doesn't matter
how much we love them.
Monogamy is too cruel a rule.
네, 있죠...
- 이거 비밀로 해줄래요?
- 걱정 말아요
Listen, can you keep this
information to yourself?
No problem.
We gotta look out for each other.
서로를 보호해줘야죠
우린 같은 족속이니까요
We're the same, you and me.
Actually, no, we're not.
사실... 달라요
Yeah, we are.
네, 같아요
아뇨, 달라요
No, we're not.
네, 같아요
Yeah, we are.
아뇨, 달라요
No, we're not.
-Okay, we're not.
-Right.
- 좋아요, 달라요
- 됐어요
But we are.
그래도 같아요
Fine. I just need to know
that you won't tell your sister.
좋아요, 혹시 해서 묻는데
동생한테 말 안 했죠?
I can promise not to tell her again.
말 안 할 게요, 다시는
자스민?
Jasmine? We met at Phoebe's
birthday party. I'm Ross Geller.
피비 생일파티 때 만났죠?
전 로스 겔러예요
You did a bad thing!
정말 너무했어요
- 알아요
- 심했어요
-Yes, I did.
-Very bad!
- 심했죠
- 아주 심했죠
-Very bad.
-Very, very bad!
그 말이 맞아요
I'm agreeing with you.
Listen, did you happen
to tell Phoebe yet?
혹시 피비에게 말했나요?
- 아뇨
- 됐어요
자스민, 제발 부탁이에요
Please. Please don't.
I love my girlfriend very much
and I want to work it out with her.
여자친구를 사랑하기 때문에
정말 잘해보고 싶어요
All right.
알았어요
Thank you. Thank you.
정말 고마워요
But you should talk to my roommate.
I told him, and he knows Phoebe too.
근데 친구에게 얘기해서
그 일을 알아요
피비와도 아는 사이구요
Who's your roommate?
친구가 누구죠?
건터! 건터!
Tell me you didn't tell Rachel about
me and the girl from the copy place.
설마 레이첼에게 복사가게
아가씨 얘긴 안 했겠죠?
미안하구만
I'm sorry.
Was I not supposed to?
그게 비밀이었나?
뭐야, 뭐? 괜찮아?
- 우린 괜찮아
- 됐어, 괜찮아
-We're all right.
-It's okay. It's okay.
-We were just waxing our legs.
-Off?
- 다리털 제거중이야
- 제거?
남자들은 죽을 때까지
경험하지 못할 고통이야
For your information, this is a pain
like no man will ever experience.
여자도 모를 고통이 있지
Unless you've been kicked in an area...
신께서 잘 보호하라고 주신
그 부분을 발로 차여봐
...that God only meant
to be treated nicely.
여자들은 남자들보다
통증에 약하잖아
Women just have a lower threshold
for pain than men, that's all.
그냥 왁스 좀 바른 거잖아
I mean, come on,
it's just a little wax.
Oh, yeah? Come here.
그래? 이리 와
유치하기는!
Oh, that's mature.
좋아, 이제 잡아당겨?
So now I just pull it off?
어서 해봐
That's right.
레이첼!
제발, 말 좀 해
Just talk to me.
Please!
Talk to you?
I can't even look at you right now.
무슨 말?
꼴도 보기 싫어
뭐야?
별 일 아냐
Nothing. Nothing.
다 잘 됐다고 했는데
-She said it was okay.
-What are they talking about?
쟤네들 왜 저래?
- 저리가!
- 그건 실수였어
-Just get away from me!
-I made a mistake, okay?
실수였다구
실수? 실수면 어쩔 건데?
갖다 버릴래?
A mistake? What were you trying
to put it in? Her purse?
뭘 버린다는 거야?
Where did he put it?
넌 다른 여자랑 잤어
You had sex with another woman!
Oh, my God!
맙소사!
무슨 일이 날줄 알았어
어제 손톱이 안 자랐거든
I knew something was wrong because
my nails didn't grow at all yesterday.
둘이 좀 다툰 후에
로스가 술이 취해서...
I guess they had a fight,
and he got drunk
You guys knew about this
and didn't tell us?
다 알면서 입 다물고
있으면 다야?
He has sex and we get hit
in our heads!
잘못은 쟤가 하고
매는 우리가 맞냐?
I want you to leave!
Just get out! Now!
당장 나가 줘
- 어서 나가!
- 싫어, 싫어
I want to stay and talk about this.
여기 남아서 얘기할 거야
그래, 좋아
All right. How was she?
어땠어?
-What?
-Was she good?
- 뭐?
- 그녀와 좋았어?
답하지 마
Don't answer that.
You said you wanted to talk about it.
Let's talk. How was she?
로스, 얘기하고 싶다며?
얘기해, 좋았냐구?
-She was....
-Awful.
그게...
- 싫었어, 끔찍했어
- 정말 별로야
-She was not good.
-Horrible. Nothing compared to you.
비교도 안돼
좀... 달랐어
She was different.
좋아? 달라?
Good different?
누구나 변화는 싫어해...
Nobody likes change.
-Just stop!
-What? Okay! Okay! Okay!
- 그만해!
- 왜? 알았어, 알았어
이제 어쩌지?
Should we do something?
레이첼한테는 거짓말하지마
Yeah. Never cheat on Rachel.
미안해, 알아? 미안해
나도 내가 혐오스러워
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
I was disgusted with myself...
...and this morning
I was upset...
오늘 아침에... 아니...
어제 화가 났다가
...and then I got your
message and I was so happy.
메시지를 듣고
너무 행복했었어
And all I wanted was to get her out
of my apartment
그때 생각난 건 오직
그 여자를 빨리 쫓아내야...
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Wait a minute.
이게 무슨 소리야?
그 아가씨, 몇 시에 갔어?
What time did your
little friend leave?
세상에, 거기 있었어?
내가 갔을 때?
Oh, my God. She was there?
She was still there?
내가 갔을 때 거기 있었다구?
She was in there when I was in there?
잠깐만... 그 여자는 내게
아무 것도 아니야
Listen, the important thing is
she meant nothing to me.
우리 관계를 걸만한
가치는 있었나보지?
And yet she was worth
jeopardizing our relationship!
우리 관계를 우습게
생각하진 않았어
I didn't think there was
a relationship.
그저 끝났다는 생각에!
-We'd broken up.
-We were on a break.
- 끝나는 중이었지
- 내 생각에 그랬단 거야
That, for all I knew, could last
forever. That is a breakup.
내겐 사형선고였어
그런 진행중도 못 참아?
You gonna get out of this
on a technicality?
I'm not trying to "get out"
of anything.
못 참아서 그런 게 아냐
그냥 우리가 끝난 줄 알았어
I thought our relationship was dead.
정신 들고 보니
끔찍했겠군!
Well, you sure had a hell of a time
at the wake.
엿듣기는 이제 그만 하자
I don't think we should listen
to this anymore.
그럼 어떡해?
나갈 수도 없는데
What are you doing?
We can't go out.
왜 안돼? 난 배고파
Why not? I'm hungry.
둘의 자존심도 생각해 줘
Because they'll know
we've been listening.
그 말을 건터한테 듣게 해?
God! And to have to hear about it
from Gunther!
나라고 그러고 싶었겠어?
I ran all over the place trying
to make sure that didn't happen!
이렇게 되는 거 막으려고
백방으로 뛰어다녔어
Oh, that is so sweet.
다정도 하셔라
I think I'm falling in love with you
all over again.
또 다시 널 사랑하고
싶어져
We can go out. They have
other things to worry about.
이제 나가야 할 것 같아
더 심한 말들이 오가기 전에
그래, 나가 보자
We'll be fine.
Rachel, I wanted to tell you.
I thought I should.
나도 말하고 싶었어
정말이야
그런데 챈들러와 조이가
하지 말래잖아
And then Chandler and Joey
convinced me not to!
왁스로 문 봉해라
절대 안 나가
Wax the door shut.
We're never leaving.
피비인데요, 9시 고객을
다른 사람한테 부탁할게요
It's Phoebe. Someone has to take
my 9:00 with Mr. Rehak...
지금 9시 15분인데
꼼짝 못하거든요
... because it's 9:15 now,
and I'm not there.
너라면 이럴 때 어떻겠어?
마크와 바람을 피웠다든지
None of this would've happened
if I didn't think...
...you were having sex with Mark?
All right.
그럼 내가 마크와 잤다면
날 용서했겠어?
Let's say I had slept with Mark. Would
you have been able to forgive me?
Yes, I would.
응, 그럴걸
마크가 내게 키스하고
나랑 침대에 누워있다면?
You'd be okay if Mark had kissed me,
and been naked with me...
...and made love to me?
응
If you knew that our hot, sweaty,
writhing bodies were
나와 정열적으로
사랑을 나누며...
그래, 기가 막히겠지
I would have been devastated...
... but I would still want
to be with you.
그래도 너와 헤어지지
않을 거야
Because, I mean, it's you.
왜냐면...
너이기 때문이야
뭐해?
무슨 생각하는지 말해봐
Come on, tell me what you're thinking.
난 지금...
I'm thinking...
... I'm gonna order a pizza.
피자를 먹고 싶어
피자라는 말은...
용서한단 뜻이야?
Order a pizza, like...
... "I forgive you"?
Oh, man!
뭐? 피자?
Pizza?
피자 좋지
I like pizza.
Put olives on the pizza.
피자에 올리브 얹어라
왁스를 먹자!
유기물이래
We could eat the wax! It's organic!
그래, 털도 잔뜩 묻었겠지
Oh, great. Food with hair on it.
No, not the used wax.
사용 안한 것도 있어
Because that would be crazy?
털은 먹기 싫어?
Could I get in on that?
Because I'm kind of hungry myself.
내가 주문할까?
나도 배고파
Fine.
됐어
Yes, I'd like to order
a large pizza.
네, 피자 큰 걸로 부탁해요
- 앤쵸비 빼고
- 앤쵸비 잔뜩 얹어주세요
-No anchovies.
-With extra anchovies.
골라내고 먹을게
That's okay.
I'll pick them off.
그걸 잘게 갈아서
소스에 넣어주시겠어요?
And could you chop some up
and put it right in the sauce?
마지막 조각은 네가 먹어
You can have the last piece
if you want.
물론이지
넌 딴 사람과 잤잖아
Well, I should think so.
You slept with someone.
They're gonna get through this,
aren't they?
이번 일 잘 해결되겠지?
Yeah. Come on, it's Ross and Rachel.
그럼, 로스하고 레이첼은
잘 해결할 거야
They've got to.
What if they don't?
만약 잘 안 되면?
걸음을 바꿔볼까?
You think I need a new walk?
뭐?
What?
고등학생 때 걸음을
지금도 하고 있거든
Well, I've been walking
the same way since high school.
You know how some guys walk into
a room and everybody takes notice?
어디든 시선을 모으는
걸음이 있잖아
'시선집중 걸음'이 필요해
I think I need a take-notice walk.
Are you actually saying these words?
그걸 지금 말이라고 하냐?
What, now you're not even
talking to me?
이젠 말하기도 싫어?
Look, Rachel, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I was out of my mind.
레이첼, 정말 미안해
정신이 나갔었나봐
I thought I'd lost you.
널 잃는다는 생각에
어쩔 줄을 몰랐어
How insane must I have been
to do something like this?
이런 짓을 할 정도로
제정신이 아니었어
I don't cheat, right?
That's not me. I'm not Joey!
바람피운 게 아냐
내 스타일이 아니야
조이랑은 다르다구
그래, 봐준다
잠깐!
지금 새벽 3시야
내 존재를 까맣게 잊었어
It's 3 a. m. They don't
know that I've come home yet.
이 시간에 어디 있는지
궁금하지도 않나?
You notice how they aren't
wondering where I am?
너도 네 생각뿐이잖아
You know, people can be
so self-involved.
이걸 생각해봐
You know what? I'm not the one
that wanted that break.
잠시 떨어져 있자고 한 건
내가 아냐
You're the one that bailed.
You're the one...
달아난 건 너였다구
순간의 일을 네가
크게 생각한 거잖아
...that ran the moment things
got rough.
-That's
-That's what?
- 그건...
- 그건 뭐?
그땐 그게 아니었어
-That is neither here nor there.
-Here we are...
그럼, 지금을 생각해
또 싸우고 있어
...in a spot again.
What do you want?
네가 원하는 게 뭐야?
어떻게 하고 싶은 건데?
How do you want to handle it?
You want to fight for us or bail?
우리를 위해 싸우는 거?
아님 도망치는 거?
내가 정말 어리석은 짓을 했어
Look, I did a terrible,
stupid, stupid thing, okay?
미안해, 되돌리고 싶지만
그럴 수가 없어
I'm sorry. I wish I could
take it back, but I can't.
I just can't see us throwing away
something we know is so damn good.
우리 좋았던 관계를
이렇게 깰 순 없어
I love you so much.
널 얼마나 사랑하는데
No, Ross! Don't!
안돼, 로스!
이러지 마
You can't just kiss me and
make it all go away.
키스만 하고 달래면
다 끝날 일이야?
이게 해결책은 아냐
그냥 덮는다고 좋아져?
It doesn't work that way.
It doesn't just make it better.
알았어
I think you should go.
이제 가봐
What?
뭐?
이제 집에 가보라구
I really think you need to go now.
오늘 아침, 우리 사이에
싸운 게 대수냐고 했지?
This morning you said there was
nothing we couldn't work out.
그땐 이럴 줄 몰랐지
What the hell did I know?
우리가 해결할 수 있는
방법이 있어
There's got to be a way we
can work past this.
I can't imagine my life without you.
난 정말...
너 없인 못 살아
Without these arms...
너의 팔...
...and your face and heart...
너의 얼굴... 너의 마음
이렇게 착한 사람을...
...your good heart, Rach, and....
안돼...
지금은 네가 타인처럼 느껴져
I can't. You're a totally
different person to me now.
I used to think of you as somebody
that would never, ever hurt me.
넌 나를 절대로 아프게 하지
않을 거라고 생각했었어
Ever.
Now I can't stop picturing
you with her.
근데 지금은 네가 그 여자와
있는 모습이 보여
I can't. It doesn't matter what you
say or what you do.
네가 무슨 말을 하든
지울 수가 없어
It's just changed everything.
모든 게 달라졌어
Forever.
영원히
생각이 바뀌진 않을까?
This can't be it.
Then how come it is?
그럼 어쩔건데?
꽤 오래 조용하네
They've been quiet for a long time.
Maybe she killed him.
로스를 죽였나봐
Let's go.
나가자
새로운 걸음걸이야?
Is that your new walk?
아니, 쉬 마려워서
No. I really have to pee.